Hangchen(Daniel) Wu

Software & Web Developer

14 Montpellier Crescent, Templestowe lower, 3107

T 0451018880 / wuhangchen2279@gmail.com / https://wuhangchen2279.github.io

A software & web developer who is proficient with a wide range of programming languages and development tools. Have a strong desire to learn more cutting edge technologies. Experience in all 5 stages of system development lifecycle including: requirement gathering, design, coding, testing, deployment, and maintenance.

EXPERIENCE

Nov 2017 -Current

Operation Feedback System

Richmond, VIC

WEB DEVELOPER

- Completely rewrite Fusion Manager that is used to configure production lines, system users, console operators, alerts, workflows, services etc.
- Daily work involves around 80% Angular and 20% Java.

Accomplishments

- Familiar with technology stack: **Angular, Java, Bamboo, Linux, Source Tree, Intellij IDE, JIRA, MySQL, Testcafe.**
- Take both roles as Developer and Tester in the team.
- Smashing tickets quickly, allowing me to take free tickets in each sprint.

Nov 2015 -Nov 2017

SPS COMMERCE

Burwood East, VIC

SOLUTION DEVELOPER

- Work on a translation engine to translate other message type (i.e. XML, CSV, SAP Idoc, etc) into EDI(Electronic Data Interchange) format.
- Maintain existing solutions and handle supporting query as needed.

Accomplishments

- Familiar with technology stack: C#, XML, XSLT, SQL, GitHub, JIRA, Visual Studio, Windows Server, Jenkins.
- Awarded for Outstanding Performance in 2016
- All projects delivered before due date

Dec 2013 -Nov 2015

FINANCIAL MANAGEMENT GROUP(Part-time)

Melbourne CBD, VIC

JAVA WEB DEVELOPER

• Develop and maintain a website - Business Coach Model.

• Update financial data on this website, and troubleshoot bugs if required.

Accomplishments

- Familiar with technology stack: Java, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, MySQL, TortoiseSVN, Eclipse, Linux.
- Upgrade back-end server to allow website run on a stable platform.
- Quick turnaround time for bug fix.

EDUCATION

2012 - 2014	MONASH UNIVERSITY MASTER OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY Scholarship: International Merit Scholarship
2012 - 2014	Shanghai Ocean University BACHELOR OF INFORMATION SYSTEM

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML & CSS & JavaScript	★ ★★☆	Angular	****
Java	* ***	C#	***
Windows & Linux & Mac	★ ★★☆	Bamboo & Jenkins	****
SQL	****	React	***

SOFT SKILLS

Fast Learner	Demonstrated ability to get familiar with my job duty within a month.
Problem Solver	Always quick turnaround time for production issue.
Can-do Attitude	A strong willingness to meet with any challenge.
Time Management	Demonstrated ability to manage multiple tasks properly
Team Player	Happy to share my ideas and suggestions in the team meeting.